LAWRENCE E. TILLSON IV

Web Developer

ABOUT LAWRENCE

Lawrence is a current student in Humber College's Web Development Program. Prior to attending Humber, he had no experience in coding whatsoever. Through hard work and an eagerness to learn, he has become fairly proficient. In Lawrence's free time he likes to learn languages, human and computer, and plays video games.

SPECIALIZATION

Most of Lawrence's education has focused on JavaScript, PHP, HTML5, CSS3, SQL, and C#. He would like to specialize in PHP.

CONTACT INFO:

10 Tobermory Dr. North York, ON M3N 2R5 416-671-2798 webdeveloper@lawrencetillson.com

SKILLS

- o 1 Year Academic Experience with Web Development
- o Proved to be Adaptive and Organized as Assistant Team Lead for the Humber Hospital Website Project.
- o Met with project leaders for multiple projects to determine scope and technical requirements.
- o Took ownership of assigned tasks and delivered the requirements.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Behavioral Therapist

UBUNTU AUTISM CONSULTING & RED HOUSE BEHAVIOR RESOURCES APRIL 2017- OCTOBER 2017 & JANUARY 2018- APRIL 2018

- Implemented skill acquisition and behavior reduction plans in an in-home setting to effectively assist the child with social skill development and manage maladaptive behaviors.
- Provided coaching, support, and guidance to the parent/guardian/caregiver in implementing the behavior reduction and skills acquisition plan.
- Collected behavioral data to monitor individual's progress and report any progress or regression in attaining objectives of behavior plan to supervisor and/or clinical director.

Retail Food Service

DUNKIN' DONUTS OCTOBER 2016 - MARCH 2017

-Ran the cash register and helped customers

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

Humber COllege

WEB DEVELOPMENT EXPECTED GRADUATION: AUGUST 2019

Simmons College

M.A. HISTORY GRADUATED DECEMBER 2017